I'm going to read a development authority for today's date and time. Item 2 is public input,
or non-schedule appearances? Don't see anybody in the audience so we'll move on
item 3 which just The Consent Agenda staff as our committee items 4 5 you put
To For approval
Which include
minutes from February 2020 then be claims From March
And April
I'll make a most true approval of the Consent Agenda as recommended.
Oh, second let's put them out at The Mike maybe whatever thing again
Who just called it?
That was Matt
Press Trustee Shaltz
Aye
Press to install
My corporate
Hi
Trustee Keller
All right
Trustee Walker
aye
Trustee Frazier
Aye
Item 6
A Mending Trust Resolution
2016-042 add
Doesn't need to sign contracts within budget capacity
I'm just going To read the background first and then if anybody has an input, they would like
Give before we
Lift a vote on it.
The original resolution was approved by
Trust On May 16th 2016 that allowed
A trust manager
True claims up $220
And amendment Resolution added
Ordesignee
Too Allowed
Members doesn't need to have the authority To negotiate, approve and execute contracts that corresponded with a fiscal year's
Fiscal Year budget capacity
This resolution would allow for an additional 20 thousand
It'd be approved pay
With The Chairman approval
And I think really
Only wording That did shift was in on
On 2nd
Did they receive this?
They had so
So
I don't know if it was red line for you all
But It says therefore their of and in additional 20 thousand dollars with the chairperson's written approval
Does anybody have any background on this?
This is Rudy, I'll give You a little back ground
So
Certainly your as Bank
We are The Council
Past Resolution that gave
The City Manager Authorization to approve up
To 20 thousand claims
If something happened, we ended
Cancelling a meeting
There was an emergency
Something came out
A year or two later
We went ahead and passed
And I'm going call it
Addendum
That allowed that number of
Double the 40
With In this case
It was not really well when it wasn't necessary
So we decided to just
Adopt that policy for all the various boards
And thats what happened
But a couple of years ago there were some language
Need To be insurved and changed
Just minor languages
but in fact
The Language had included
In my case
Mayor Oring
That allowed that left out
So all we are doing is fixing
It's not really a script or error
But just at oversight of leaving
Language
This authority has always been there
but I think Melissa caught it
When the situation came up last
Monastered Joe called
And so, he was trying to fix
Thats kind Of The Background
We're Not asking
Authorities approve anything
Brand new
Hasn't Been Done in A Pass
And then Is it Just Standard Operating
Procedure the City for
Basically All The Authorities and Borders
Social Planion is Recording to
Yeah
If
It's necessary To invoke
Either they original 20,000
Or you know a subsequent
20 thousand
At that very next Board
Meaning Requirement
As at Trust Manager
We're Poofed That
Two of them board
For Information Sake
So was This Did Just Come Out
Because Something Came Up That Required
A $40,000 Approval?
It came About Originally
because the sound system
The Work On that Sound System
Was Done I Think
And In Voice was 25 thousand
Dollars in Round Numbers
We ended up Cancelling a Meeting
But They Need To Be Paid
So What Dean Did
Because He Had The Authority Do
so Was It Approved the First 20,000
And We Just Told him
Were Not Gonna Be All A Payed
To Other Fives and Tillers
Meeting
Hell to approve That Subsequent Five
I Think There was Another Delay for
Some Reason
If i Would Authorize
Additional 5,00
Payment
Whatever Lay Your Date
And I Said Yes and So Then
Is Geo Got To Looking At It
She said, Oh First Off
Rudy's Not Supposed to Be
Authorizing Because He is not
The Chairman Of This Board
Any More A
In B That Extra 5000
There'S No Provision For it
We're Just Trying
Fixed that But Thats What
Triggered It
Come Back Up As An Issue
Man Everybody Say
Wait a minute.
Need Decline up this Language
Okay
You Have Emotion To Approve
Imending Trust Resolution
Like The Motion To Approve
As Recommended
Was That Matt?
Yes
Okay, Man
Thats Fine
Real Call
I
Steak Counter
Steak Stole
Hi
Decline Work
Steak Fires
Right Item 7
Budget Amendment
20-31
And This Is the Expitting
99 for 90 Money For A New Sound System
Mr. Dylan D What i Talk On That It All
It Was
Just Mark This Door
Is the 90 for 90 Money
Wasn't Actually Included In
Vicious Budget
is this money That was Coming
Yet But wasn'T Here When The
Budge Of A Set Up
So Its Put in Another Account
And We're Just Moving Into
An account so that we Can
Make That Pay Okay
Do You Have Any Questions or
Concerns For As Promotion?
I'll make a Most To Approve
The Budgeon Amendment
On All Second
Was Thats you Matt
No Still Wrong
Right OK, Romney
So This I Think
Drop It
Press A Rarity or
That's Just
Awesome
It's So
Right
The Calors,
Not Pressing Forkons
Pressing Fragure
Chairman Orbit
OK Moving On To
Before Actually We Go to Item 8
a couple of Weeks ago
i had reached out
Of Marsha
About Grant
that was available for
Non-profits
Five Wancy 3 is actually the College
as well Through
Oklahoma Humanities
In Thenton Mr. Dylan
was gracious enough to
Write That Grant
So I'm Just Going To Read The
Letter that We Receive From
Them It Says Dear Danny
i Im Very Glad Report
the Oklahoma Humanities
As Approved Your Application
for Funding Through
O'Klooma Hope Grant
They Will Take A Few Days
Definalized This
With Our Board of Directors
Of Processed and Ness
Sir, Pay Work
Hopes Have The Official Grant
Pippework Ready
Send You Next Week
And Then we Should Be
able Get an Electronic
payment If 10000 sent
to You Soon After.
At That Point, We Would Just
Be Waiting For The National
Endowment for the Humanities
To Rout Us
THE Ness Sorry Funds
that Will Direct
TO YOU
And you said There'll be
there's an additional amount
Then Think As I Read it
Rowling On It Get To
Rowling on It Getting To
Rowling Going Go To get
10000 we'd Originally Asked
Four Fifteen Okay
and DoYou Want Talk About What
Were going
Doing With Those Fund?
Yes This Opportunity
Was Sassetta
An International Level
In Really Their Main
Focus was four
salaries
They didn't want people
losing their jobs
So we kind of Fetched that
Most Of This would be
To maintain the
salaries
And We also included with it
Money
Through By A Portable
Disinfector
That Will Out Us to
Short amount
At Time, Go through In
Our Entire Facility
and Disfecting
ForThat
I Don' Which was
I Think It's Gonna Be About
$760
Like That
And Then 20 Gallon
The Disinfectant
22 Gallons
Against
100 Boxes Of
Just Postable Gloves
that' All We Put Into
the Grand
Proposal
In Their Favorite
Except it Basically A
Spray Machine
Being
Expressed a Distance
Effective.
Yeah
That is Going To
Be Huge
Benefit As far as
Off Setting
Paying Those Employees
And Congratulations
That' Exciting New
CITERUS
Any Thoughts Comments On
that?
Is there a promotion
No
I just
Okay
Marcia, Do You Have Something
Before
She's Just Moving
Take Their Pull
Oh okay
Gotcha
If There'S Nothing Else
Item Eight A Journey Met
This is Rudy
All Make A Motion To
A Journey
Land Second of It
Hi
Bestie Coward
All Good
Hi, Thank You All